Now we are going to jump into the sub sales processes,
discovery call analysis, proposal, scope, workflows,
and then some bonus material.
Today we're just gonna do discovery.
So the point of the discovery call,
there's a number of points of this.
I talked a little about this yesterday with like our form
and filling out questions.
I am very particular about who I get on the phone with.
And again, that doesn't mean
because I'm some super important person.
That should also apply to you too.
You don't wanna talk to people who
are not serious about hiring you.
And, and, and granted, that could come with a caveat
of like, oh, maybe they're in an agency relationship
for another 90 days, and then that's fine.
I'm talking about people that don't know what you do,
aren't really overly educated on SEO too, right?
If they're just like, you know,
I don't mean this in a disrespectful way,
but like my dad, if he was like, oh,
I heard about this thing called like SOEI have a website.
Like, tell me, like, you don't wanna get on
a, a call with those types of folks.
So we wanna make sure we screen them out
through the booking process.
That means no phone calls.
You know, you can have an email, that's fine.
Dms, that's, that's fine.
But I'm talking about like a streamlined process
through a singular point of conversion that runs
to a booking calendar.
Not a form prevent you from a lot of spam.
And also just chasing people down.
It's another thing too, like form leads are chase leads.
That means you have to then con,
like somebody submits a form
and then you have to contact them.
You want to get a booked appointment on
their calendar, on your calendar.
It's by far the most effective
and, uh, it's just the, the most effective way to do it.
So that leads directly to the discovery call.
We're gonna go through that in detail,
but the discovery call is more qualification.
So what we're doing is we're asking leads,
qualifying questions, leading questions
that are gonna help us to collect information on whether
or not we're a good fit for them, you know, to,
to move forward to the next stage, which is the analysis
and proposal, which is quite a bit of work.
So we don't want to be just breezing people through this.
We really wanna make sure that we're getting buy-in on
objectives, on expectations and on pricing as well.
Even if you don't have it scoped out, we all kind of know
what a campaign is gonna cost.
You should be sharing that information
with them on these calls, and I'll show you how to do
that in a way that doesn't scare them off.
But we wanna make sure that we're
getting verbal buy-in on those things.
Otherwise, we're gonna waste cons at time.
So let's go ahead and dive in here for the discovery call.
I have a template for you that we're gonna look at
for a second, but
before we get on the call,
let's talk about preparation for it.
So, played football in college,
I put this in here, it says, have an idea.
It's not our football coach should always like, yell at us,
like, have an idea, son.
That means like, you know, the, the, I play defense,
the offense is running a play, like, you know,
the formation, like have an idea of what they're doing.
Is a runner's a path? You know,
the the point is it just means just
prepare for the call a little bit.
We don't wanna show up and pull up their information,
be like, oh, you're a lawyer, that's cool.
Like, we want to come prepare.
It builds trust and rapport with them.
It shows that you are about business too, right?
So what's great is, is that if you're using
that Calendly format that I showed you,
you're gonna have their website,
you're gonna have their budget, you're gonna have
their current agency relationship,
what they're investing in,
you're gonna have all that information.
And that's more than enough, honestly,
just their website is, is is more than enough.
That's why you always wanna make sure to ask
for website, not just email.
'cause if they give you a Gmail,
sometimes they can be hard to find.
So what I like to do is 15 really five minutes, five,
10 minutes before the call, I'll set up this file.
I don't really use this anymore
for the purpose of illustration.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna pretend like I use this file
and I'm gonna walk you through it step by step.
But make a copy of this.
Add in, you know, add it to your sales Google Drive folder,
and that you'll have notes on every single discovery call
that you do, which is important.
If you're passing it to, you know, a VA
or a support staff to help you
with the analysis and proposal.
Then you can also add in the call recording there
for them to watch as well.
So, 15 minutes beforehand, I'll do it,
and then I'll just drop their website into
atress or SEMrush.
And really what I'm looking at is twofold, right?
I'm looking at current performance.
Is it going up, is it going down?
How much traffic they're getting, the value of the traffic,
what type of keywords they're ranking for.
Very, very, very simple high level stuff.
I'm not doing an analysis.
This is just for context to have a conversation
to see which way I can lead it,
because it's a much different discovery process if the
website's going up and crushing it,
versus if the website's going down.
If the website's going up and crushing it,
it's probably not gonna be like a you, you,
you're gonna wanna understand what,
like why do you want an agency if this is happening?
Are you turning off an agency? Do you have an in-house team?
See what I'm saying? So it's gonna guide the questions
that you ask to have a much more productive conversation.
And then of course, like I said, just going through
what they filled out, you know, I'll go to their website
to always look at their website.
I'll see for, for us working with attorneys, I'll look at
how many attorneys do they have,
how many locations do they have?
I'll take a quick peek at their like Instagram
or YouTube just to see
if they're creating content on social.
Again, just context, right?
It's just information that you can use
to have a much more productive conversation with them.
So I'm gonna go ahead and show you this template real quick.
Just make a copy of it, save it to your blueprint stuff.
And then every time you want to use it again,
you just make a copy of this
and then save it to your sales folder.
Google Drive. So we go through this, I've got slides
to accompany this as well.
We'll go through these kind of one by one,
but lemme just run you through this template real quick.
So again, you just put in the name prospect, email,
phone number, et cetera.
Just goes you through this, through this process.
Again, again, just reiterating this information for y'all.
And then the first part of the call,
I usually have 30 minutes booked for these calls, right?
So the, the first part of the call, rapport building,
we're talking like a couple minutes, right?
We're not going 15, 20 minutes into chit chat.
This is, Hey, where are you located? Awesome.
I've been there before. Or you got plans
for the holidays, what do you got going on?
You have family. Oh, okay, awesome, me too, right?
Just like finding small pieces
to connect with them on stuff.
What's your role of the company? Are you the owner?
Are you the internal marketing person?
How long you been there? That's cool. And how'd you find us?
This, this is important.
'cause for me, this gives me some context on the
conversation again for like, oh,
I've been watching YouTube videos for years, versus like,
oh, I just saw an ad and I clicked.
Then I know how much
to tell them about us on that call as well.
So I'm gonna jump back into the slides here.
Again, all this is in, in this document here for you two
for notes, but I put in the slides here,
It's a a little bit cleaner to look at.
So we'll just look it over here. So it's just
mirroring exactly what's in the document.
You're not missing anything by, by jumping over here.
So again, finding common ground, you know, sports,
current events, business success, location, family stuff,
whatever you can, there's a lot of books on sales,
you know, uh, what is it?
Never Split the difference. I think that's the book
that's written by like the FBI host negotiator.
One of the things that always stood out to me,
there was just, uh, the concept
of finding common ground with somebody.
It's important, you know, like people
ultimately in this business, in any business,
they do business with people that they like.
So it's important to try and the, the fastest
and easiest way is to try and find some sort
of common ground with somebody.
And it could be, you know, kids, it could be marriage,
it could be where they're located, a whole bunch of stuff.
We wanna try and find some very basic
common ground to kick things off.
Just get some good energy flowing through.
So then we go into the leading questions.
So leading questions are gonna be questions
that help you steer the conversation
and to determine if, one,
if your service is a good fit for them.
But two, if if they're a good fit for you.
That's, that's a very important thing here too.
This is, we wanna make them feel like
this call is for them, right?
But ultimately this is just as much about us
because we do not wanna waste time.
You don't wanna waste time you don't want to.
A lot of reasons why. You know, I think one
of the biggest complaints about
agency sales is ghosting, right?
People are like, ah, man, it ghosted me.
I haven't heard from 'em. We're like, I've gotten
to the finish line and I haven't heard from 'em.
That's usually because the,
they just weren't fully qualified, right?
Like the proposal was like, it was a pricing thing,
it was a scope thing, it was a timing thing.
They weren't ready, that wasn't communicated.
A whole bunch of stuff, right? And really what
that comes down to, if somebody's ghosting you,
just like in the dating world, that
just means they're not that interested.
And we wanna reduce that
because one that's stressful and two, it's a waste of time.
That's your resources and time that you're wasting.
So we only want to send out proposals to people
that are fully ready embedded, right?
We don't wanna waste time and resources doing that.
So, you know, when I look at my pipeline,
there is a big discrepancy between calls booked,
discovery calls taken, proposals sent,
and then deals closed, right?
And that window gets smaller.
So like we get a good amount of leads,
I'll probably cancel like
25% of 'em 'cause they're not qualified.
And then after the discover call,
like another 15% don't move forward.
So we're talking about maybe 50 per five 0%,
if my math is right, or 60% of of leads
that booked to get proposals.
And then we'll close about half of those, right?
So you can see how it's like a, like a,
like a funnel that goes down, right?
But the closer we can get to proposals sent
and deals closed, that's really the number
that we want to optimize against.
You know, like that's
what I look at from a sales point of view.
When I'm looking at our pipeline, it's not so much,
how many leads did we get this month?
It's how many proposals did we send, right?
Like when I sit and talk with Jan,
who does all our Facebook ads in, in marketing
and media, I, you know, he tends to report down leads
and I'm like, I don't like, just
because they booked a call on
my calendar doesn't make them a lead.
I mean, technically it does, I guess,
but like to me a lead is somebody who gets a proposal.
That's what I want to categorize as a lead
because that's the data and metric that makes sense
for actually growing and scaling this business.
So, bit of a tangent there,
but you know, we have to qualify them, right?
So these are some questions that you can use.
You know, I usually will start with something about,
tell me a little about the law firm and,
and tell me what you've done for marketing to date.
I usually join, join those two together.
Tell me about firm and what you've done
for marketing to date, to date.
You know, I talked about this yesterday, right?
This is about them, not you.
So if you find yourself doing most
of the talking on a discovery call,
especially in the first 20 minutes, pause, reset,
and go back to these questions
because this is not a proposal call.
Like you are not proposing services.
This is a discovery call. You wanna discover about them.
Your time will shine, your time will come to shine.
But this isn't it, especially in the first half to 75%
of the call, we wanna make sure that, you know,
we're giving them the time and attention to talk about them.
And people love talking about themselves too.
It's another great way to build rapport.
People love talking about their business
and again, this is very valuable information for it.
So I'll ask them too, you know,
and when it comes to the marketing,
like what do you think you need help with?
Like what, what is it that you're
looking for from an agency?
Help and support. How many staff do you have?
Resources, are you spending money on paid
search and advertising?
These are also context clues, right?
To understand do they have the budget?
It's one thing to say, yes, I can spend X amount.
And it's another thing to say,
how much are you currently spending?
And without directly asking them that there's ways
that we can extract that information without asking them
directly, how much are you spending on this work
with other agencies or contractors?
What does that look like? What are your goals
and expectations from working with an agency?
Important question. What we see
as success and how do you measure success?
So these are all questions,
this is more than enough information here to start
to understand, you know, get the conversation flowing
and really getting them talking about them, right?
And again, we need to get them to request a proposal.
That's the main goal. We'll talk more about how to do that.
So after we get through that,
I'll go into the elevator pitch portion of this,
which is really kind
of your time now to talk about yourself.
So, you know, this is
where I also said, how did you find us?
I'll ask that in the beginning of the call.
'cause this'll inform me here about
what I need to push here as well.
And this is your time to sell.
You, you really don't want to undersell yourself here
because this is, again, you have a window
of opportunity here to get them to say, okay, yeah,
I'm interested in a proposal from you.
Right? So what I like to do is, is, is,
is in intake the information that they gave me,
and I'm listening for cues, right?
I'm looking at their, their their SEO traffic.
I'm seeing what's happening and I'm trying
to understand the areas of opportunity
that I can pull different levers, um,
and send little jabs and pitches, right?
So it's not just this space here where it's like, Hey,
I'm Ryan Stewart, I do this and this and that.
It's really trying to sell through,
I don't wanna say like stories,
but like, you know, through stories of other clients.
So something I use that works a lot is,
I just closed a deal yesterday actually using this line
where I said, we actually had a law firm morphing law.
You could check out the case study on our website
came in exactly where you were.
Criminal defense lawyer wanted
to do some personal injury stuff.
We started doing SEO and PPC
and now his name's all over our website.
Like, we can do the same thing for your firm
that works really well.
Now, you might not have case studies, that's fine,
it doesn't have to be a case study.
But if you can relate what their problems are
and their campaigns are to previous stuff, it gets a lot
of buying and trust a, a, a a ton, right?
Because people want to be able to see and visualize success.
And it's very easy to do that if they have, you know,
another company that you've done that for.
If you don't have that, if you're like, well, Ryan,
I'm just getting started, I don't have any success.
Sell yourself, right?
You know, I like to talk about
how long I've been doing this for.
I like to talk about, you know, the fact that one of
what my proudest things in business wise, not,
not personally wise, is the fact
that we take pride in our marketing
and we spend our own money on advertising.
So I'll use this line all the time where I say, look at,
you know, I spend 30, $40,000 a month on my own marketing
and advertising, so I know exactly
what it's like to sit where you sit.
It's scary, it's a gamble.
This is not a guaranteed investment.
This takes a certain level of stomach
to be able to go forward with.
But I understand that because I do it myself.
And you can see that online.
Check out our YouTube channel, check out our Instagram,
we live and breathe this stuff.
That's another really good pitch that I use
because again, it does two things.
One, it's like, okay, like we got the chops.
We believe in this so much that we do it for ourselves.
And two, it's kind of calling them out to be like,
it takes it, I get it.
Like, but it it, it takes some
stones to spend money like this.
And like, do you have what it takes? You know?
And I don't say that obviously,
but it kind of, it, it, it, it, it stirs up a little bit
of competition, which I think is healthy.
So, you know, again, this is your time to
sell yourself and your company.
This is a line from, I don't if anyone's seen Seinfeld,
there was like a po there was like a question there,
like one of, I had to do a polygraph
and George Costanza was like,
it's not a lie if you believe it.
So I'm not telling you to lie, but I, I understand that some
of you are maybe newer in this
and you gotta believe in yourself.
You gotta sell yourself a little bit.
If you don't have the track record
or you know, you're not doing your own marketing
yet, you're just getting started.
You might have to put a little bit of
lipstick on a pig, right?
You might have to, you know, just dig deep
and really sell yourself and sell your company, uh, on,
on why you're a good fit to solve this problem.
And part of that too, right? A lot
of people ask about case studies, like,
I don't have case studies on this.
The need for case studies comes from prospects
who don't trust that you can get the job done, right?
If a lot of people are like,
and I get it, people ask us for, for references and,
and case studies, they, they do that for us too.
So it's, it's, it's, it's a very commonplace thing.
But a lot of the times people are asking for that
because it's coming from a place of like, well,
I've been burned before and you know, I wanna see that.
I wanna, I wanna hear
from somebody else that you've done before.
But, and, and if you don't have
case studies, there's nothing you do about that.
That's just, it is what it is.
But you can beat a lot of that back in the beginning stages
of your agency by showing
that you know what their problem is.
Communicating that problem back to them,
pitching them a good service,
and then selling yourself on being able to solve
that problem for them.
That, and at the end of that is when people, you know,
will ask for, like, Hey, do you
have references that I can check with?
You know, I just wanna make sure that X, y, z
but you know, we've, you know,
when I was just getting started too,
I was able to beat that back.
'cause I didn't have case studies or testimonials
or references that I could send in the legal space, right?
'cause lawyers won't usually wanna talk to other lawyers.
So, you know, you just gotta sell yourself.
And, and this is where kind
of like the selling comes into play.
But again, this isn't like a hard close.
This isn't like, hey, like I'm offering you a discount
that's gonna be gone by the new year.
So gimme a decision now it's, I can do this.
I know what your problem is. I've done
this a million times before.
I might be smaller than other a other agencies.
I might not have the experience
or track record that a lot
of the agencies say that they have.
But I can do this and I can prove it to you, right?
Like, we can help you get to the goals that you told us.
We just need a shot. I go through this a lot
because in the grand scheme of things, in the legal space,
I'm late to the game and we're pitching against agencies
that are 10 times the size of us.
And you know, we lose, I lost a deal last week
to a larger agency who does crap work,
but they have the longer track record
and that's fine, I get it.
But man, I was, I put up a pitch to 'em
and I almost had 'em, but they were like, yeah, you know,
we, we have a 30 person marketing team on it.
I, I don't think you, like we have more internal
people than you have at your agency.
I don't think you can handle this account. And that's fine.
Maybe we couldn't, but I'll be damned if I wasn't gonna try
and get it and deliver on it too.
So, so again, kind of going back to
the initial scoping that you did here, this is
where we can start to push them into the proposal stage.
So I kind of like, I guess o over push the, the dis the,
if we talk about timelines, right?
Like if this is a 30 to 40, 30,
we'll call it a 30 minute call, right?
Two minutes of rapport building five to eight minutes
of discovery questions, leading questions,
having them talk about themselves, two minutes
to three minutes talking about yourself and your experience.
Kind of like getting them to perk up a little bit.
And now we can also start
to talk about the initial opportunities.
So the initial opportunities come from that.
Like age reps looking at it, looking at their website
and a lot of stuff is pretty basic, right?
So if their traffic is going
down, it's pretty straightforward.
It's like, Hey, you know, like I noticed since May
of last year that your, your traffic's been going
down, let's talk about that.
You know, like, did you migrate websites?
You know, blah, blah, blah. So you can get a little bit more
specific here with what you're seeing.
And, and you know, again, if you're pitching SEO
or Facebook ads or you know, all these different things,
when I'm pitching Facebook ads, I'm looking at their
Instagram account being like, well, like, you know,
you're not, you're not creating any video.
Let me show you how. Like, let me show you a script.
Let me show you a client video that we've
done, blah, blah, blah, et cetera.
So again, it's just, it's just areas of opportunity.
It's not a proposal, it's not an analysis.
It's literally just to get them
to dangle the care to get to the next step.
And you know, a lot of lines that I'll use here is, there's
so much opportunity for you.
I'm excited for you. So I say, I say that one all the time,
I'm like, man, like I'm excited about this campaign
because you have no traffic.
So like, I know for a fact that we can crush this
before, I've said that
before, like, we'll get a
website in that's got like no traffic.
I'm like, hey, like, we'll crush this. You know what I mean?
Like, you, you've run a successful business with this.
Imagine what would happen if we can a hundred xs you know,
in the next six to 12 months.
There's a few small changes
and you're gonna see a lot more
trafficking leads in revenue.
I, I, I promise you that.
And I can show you a roadmap
that's gonna show you exactly how we can help you do that.
So again, this is about opportunities for growth, not issues
that will cost 'em to fix.
These are like small psychological things.
Again, a lot of agencies want to come out and pitch
and just talk about themselves and talk about services
and you know, we do q research and this and that.
Like when I hear that, I'm like, oh my God,
the costs are starting to stack up.
I want to hear if I'm on a a discovery sales
call, I wanna hear about myself.
I wanna hear that you understand what my business is,
who our customer is, our issues with performance, you know,
my gripes about past agencies that I've worked.
I want to hear that. I want you
to understand that and feel that.
And I want you to be able to, to, to be like, yeah, dude,
this like, we're gonna crush this.
You know? So this is to entice them to ask
for a full proposal because at the end of this, you know,
we're ultimately gonna ask them for a proposal call.
So before I do that, I'm not just like, Hey,
do you want a proposal analysis?
I'll ask them this. Where are you in the process?
Are you talking to other agencies?
Are you looking for proposals?
There's a lot of opportunity here, a lot of stuff
that we can work on, but I wanna make sure
that the timing is right for you.
Let them talk. Very good line. I use that all the time.
It, it tells me what sometimes be like.
And again, but we're trying now we're starting
to remove the objections from the ghosting in the future of,
yeah, you know, I'm with an agency and I'm shopping around
and I'm like, you know, if they say, oh, we'll say that.
We'll hear that a lot. We'll be like, they're like, okay,
you have an agency, what does the contract look like?
It's a 12 month contract. What month are you in?
We're in month two. Can you get outta
that co Are you prepared to get outta that contract?
I don't know, we're just shopping around.
I'm not gonna do a proposal for 'em.
I'll say, look, it, I totally understand,
but you know, our analysis
and proposal takes about four hours worth of work.
A lot of other people charge for it.
So I would just, I would, I would ask
that we hold off on this until, you know,
you're within striking distance of potentially moving on
or moving to a new agency.
You know, and I'll be like, look, we do these all the time
for people and they give them to their agency
and they do the work and then, you know,
we don't, we don't charge for it.
That's not how we operate. So I say that all the time.
So this is how we, I kind
of like will not move from discovery to this is the really,
really important questions that we need to ask to make sure
that we are in alignment with where they are in the process.
So if they say that, yeah, they're looking for proposals,
I will also talk very quickly just about costs.
Again, removing that objective.
We don't want to do a four hour proposal analysis
and then pitch it to them and get to the end of it
and then have them be like, ah, wow, this is expensive,
but thank you for this awesome document.
So I'll always say something like, look, I mean,
and again, you know what it's gonna cost.
So I'll say something like, look,
I know cost is important on these campaigns.
These can get outta control.
I just want to tell you a ballpark of what it would cost.
So that way we can get on the same page if that's something
that you'd want to move forward with.
And I'll tell, I'll say, usually for
personal injury lawyer in Florida, we're looking at six
to $10,000 a month.
Does that sound something that would be in your reach?
Does that sound okay?
And if they're like, I'd be like, okay, I understand.
Well, you know, there's other things that we can do.
We usually don't get to that point. I can usually tell when
you do this for long enough, looking at their website,
how many people they have on staff,
how many locations do they have?
Are they active on social media?
It's like their Instagram is dead. Nothing.
If they have one attorney on staff, one location,
I'm probably not, I'll probably still go through this
'cause I might change the pitch to advertising instead.
But usually SEI won't, I want end to pitching them to that.
So I already know this stuff. But again, that's
to get verbal buy-in
because as we get through this whole process, again,
there's always questions about follow ups
and like the aggressive sales,
like do I call 'em, do I text 'em?
You are setting the framework for that now
by building in accountability for them, right?
You're removing objections here, like removing objections
of, oh, well I'm gonna, I'm,
I'm in a contract or I'm not ready.
Well, I asked you that two weeks ago
and you said that you were in market two.
Ah, this is a lot more than I thought it was gonna be.
Well, I told you before I put this together a ballpark range
of how much it was gonna cost.
And you said that that was okay, what changed, right?
So we're, we're taking these big objections away from
them all the way upstream.
So that way in two weeks when we are supposed
to have an expected decision on our service,
they're not gonna give you the runaround or ghost on you
because, and then you can aggressively follow up with 'em
because you could say, Hey, look it, you told me
by this date that you would have a decision for me.
I'm gonna call you, I'm gonna text
you until you gave me a decision.
So again, we're still in discover call here.
Not to get too far in advance here,
but we are just trying to get one verbal buy-in on, yeah,
I'm in market two, the pricing seems okay,
that's something I can work with.
And three, get them to request a proposal.
So after we talk about pricing, we'll say,
all right, well let's talk about next steps.
Next steps is my team does an for you,
it's an analysis and a proposal.
It's very, very detailed.
A lot of other agencies charge for it as an audit.
We do it for free because I can't properly scope out your
campaign unless I know exactly
what is going on underneath the hood.
So we take the time and effort to do this upfront.
Are you open to that? Is that something
that you wanna move forward with?
And we get them to say yes.
And then if they give you the green light,
you cannot get off the call without the following.
You have to book a follow
call while you have 'em on the phone.
You have to have to have to have to do that.
Because again, the last thing
that you wanna be doing is trying to follow up over email
and doing the whole, Hey, I'm free Tuesday, Thursday,
Friday from one two, and then it gets booked.
It just, then they don't answer emails, get it booked,
get it on their calendar, get it accepted.
So I'll literally have my calendar open
and I'll have my screen shared
and I'll say, do you wanna pop up in your calendar?
You see what I have open?
Does any of this time work for you?
And then I'll send them the invite on the call
and make sure that they get it on the call.
Because again, we do not wanna waste time
and resources going through this
unless they're fully ready to be able to do that.
So there's a little homework here as we wrap up today's call
for the discovery call.
You can make a copy of this template,
it's gonna be distributed in school for you.
And just kind of go through the questions on your own,
take a look at 'em, customize them
to whoever you're working with.
Just really think about, it's good to have this too.
Again, when you, if you've been doing this for a while,
that's fine, you don't need this.
But it's really good to have a frame framework in front
of you if like, you're not comfortable with sales
or you're just getting started, this is proven.
Everything that I just told you here is proven
to work in agency sales
and you don't want to miss them, right?
Like, you don't want
to miss important steps in this process.
You don't wanna forget to tell 'em about pricing.
You don't wanna forget to get them booked.
You don't wanna forget to pitch yourself, right?
So like, it could be helpful for you to write down
what your elevator pitch is and just have that done.
And then you can have it open when you're talking to them.
You know, sometimes I used to, when I was kind
of first getting started with this stuff, I would have this
document open and I would share my screen
and I would be taking notes on the screen
and they would see me do that and they loved it.
People love when you're taking notes.
They know that you're listening. We use all these like AI
note takers now that nobody checks, honestly.
But you know, when people see you taking
notes, I love it personally.
Whenever I'm talking to someone, I see 'em taking notes,
I'm like, hell yeah, please, thank you.
Write it down. When I don't see people taking notes,
I'm like, are you gonna write that down?
You know what I mean? I'm, I'm,
I'm giving you a lot of information.
Are you gonna write this down? You know, it's like when you
go to a restaurant and you put in like 50 things
and they're like, yeah, yeah, no, I got it.
And then they come out and they, then they mess it up.
It's like, yeah, I told you to write it down.
You know, it's almost kinda like, it's a, it's like a sound
of courtesy to me when you, when you write things down.
So, you know, you can share your screen
and just go through the, the,
the questions here that you have.
You know, you can just change the titles here a little bit.
You can just kind of delete this stuff.
But like, you know, you put your notes in here.
And again, I know you have like AI note takers,
but like, I also know that you don't check them.
Nobody ever does anybody check those things?
Nah, that's what I thought. Nobody checks them.
You get the email summary and you, you check it
for two seconds, then you're, you're done.
This is good because then when you're putting together the
proposal, you've got notes for whoever's doing it.
And this stuff also carries through to delivery.
This is something I'm very adamant about with my team,
which is I wanna make sure that our service is consistent
and congruent with what the sales conversations
that I'm having with prospects.
Because it's not a good look if they tell you something
and then it's really important to them
and it doesn't get pushed forward into what you're actually,
what they're actually paying you for.
I've literally just had this conversation today
because we're starting to take on a lot more SEO deals
and I, I had a, like a kind of a town hall
with all of our SEO team today.
I was like, look like I wanna get on the same page
with you guys because I wanna make sure that I'm not,
my mouth isn't writing checks that we can't cash.
So like, let's go through our process, let's go through
what you guys are seeing working.
I wanna make sure that we're getting on the same page so
that way when I'm, when I'm passing you clients,
you guys are consistent, congruent on point.
We never drop the ball. That stuff is so, so,
so important in this business.
So that's all we got for today for discovery on.